[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Elizabeth"]}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "How would you describe the occasion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "It was -- you know, it was very much how we've been around Elizabeth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "What was she like as a godmother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "She was lovely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "I think better than most people, didn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "She really did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Yes, she did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Describe to me since you're one of the very few people to be there, what was the atmosphere like through the day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "You know, it was a fairly short ceremony.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "That's just amazing to watch, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Oh, it's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "WP", "POS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What do you think is probably the biggest misconception about Elizabeth Taylor from your experience of knowing her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "You know, it's hard to say because I knew her as a person, and I don't know her as what's in the public eye.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "And Jose, finally, if you could use one word to sum up Elizabeth Taylor, what word would you go for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Oh, unique in every which way.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Is your life as good as I imagine it to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "My life is pretty damn good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "You don't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "And if I do, I complain about some of the things I've got, I'd be being kind of a sissy about some things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "I am?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "With this movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "That's strong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Cool, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Yes, that's cool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "ORGAN: Yes, what would he think of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "He'd love that, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "How much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Just enough that my kids aren't going to have to worry about themselves, but enough that they're going to have to work for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "A nice egg?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Yes, you know that egg -- I have the number that I'm going, OK, I'm going to be fine, my lady is going to be fine, my kids are going to be fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "But do you still have to worry about bills?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Don't have to worry about them, but we're pretty thrifty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "What's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, I spent one summer with my brother shoveling mushroom compost.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "It was sheep dung.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "What did it give you, shoveling compost?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Well, if you're too high on your horse, as my mom would say, shoveling some sheep dung for 20 days in the middle of nowhere is probably a good thing for you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Was the dream there then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "I don't think it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Were you a fan of the movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I saw two films before I was 17.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 315, "question": "What were they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "\"Orca\" and \"King Kong.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1953"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Green Bay Packers"]}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Because your dad was a football player?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "He used to play for the Green Bay Packers in 1953.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "And it hadn't been a career path, when was the moment you suddenly thought, OK, maybe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "There was a day -- and mind you, there were many days leading up to this, but I was becoming restless with the idea of heading towards law school, which is what I thought I was going to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Were you relieved at the reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Oh, I was relieved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "He was artistic as well as sporty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Does part of you think ever, I would have quite liked to have been a lawyer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "No, not that much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "She's got soccer practice tomorrow, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Do you think you're the first client to ever threaten me and my family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "All I said was she's pretty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "You don't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "They're not the first ones I go see when I leave to go out to the theater.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Do I ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "-- comedy?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "If it had to be one or the other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CD", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "You like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "-- it's very pacey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "One what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Jammy Git.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "-- England -- England, what does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "It's an English euphemism for very lucky man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England", "England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "I mean you struck gold, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I would agree with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "And they -- I mean they are very exotic people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Is that what attracted you to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I mean there's a -- you know, I spoke of her grace earlier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 594, "question": "What was going on there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "I mean, that's a great --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "-- to not want to get married?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Are you against marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Do you think you will get married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 632, "question": "And how's fatherhood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Fatherhood is a --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "-- as good as you thought and hoped it would be?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "It's like even now, you look back with affection, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "You first noticed he never had his shirt on, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 776, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 777, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "What did Martina say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "Enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 833, "question": "You love these things, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 834, "answer": "I like drums.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mishka", "Just Keep Livin Records"]}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "Mishka?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "Well, Mishka, he's with my record level -- label, Just Keep Livin Records.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", ":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 856, "question": "Is that something that you aspire to or is there something else that's more significant to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "IN", "POS", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 857, "answer": "Work-wise, I mean, that would be -- that would be an honor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 868, "question": "You play the bongos?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 869, "answer": "We do the soundtrack.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 886, "question": "And even though you don't want to put yourself through any kind of epitaph, if I held you down and forced you to, what would you like on the Matthew McConaughey tombstone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 887, "answer": "Jeez --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew McConaughey"]}}]